Guide to the Lucien L. Nunn papers [ca.1863-1971]
Nunn, Lucien L. papers [ca.1863-1971]
- Series VI. Photographs
  - Places: Survey Photography, Landscapes, Interiors, etc.
    - A. Electrical, Mining, and Mill Interests
      - 114 - Bear Lake - dredging - n.d. (Box 47)
      - 115 - Telluride - street scenes - ca. 1914 (Box 53)
      - 116 - Ophir - landscape - n.d. (Box 53)
      - 117 - unidentified location - animas line and transformer house, men on pole - n.d. (Box 53)
      - 118 - Timpanogos River - n.d. (Box 53)
      - 119 - Camp Bird Divide relief station - 1940s (Box 53)
      - 120 - Grace Station - regarding burned switch - n.d. (Box 53)
      - 121 - near Grace, Idaho - second crossing of Last Chance Canal - n.d. (Box 49)
      - 122 - near Camp Bird Divide - Camp Bird Mill and local area - 1905 (Box 49)
      - 123 - Battle Creek - Station Building - 1909 (Box 49)
      - 124 - map - The Electrical Distributing Lines and Waterways of the Telluride Power Company - n.d. (Box 49)
      - 125 - Niagara - Niagara Power Station - annotated - ca. 1905 (Box 40)
      - 126 - Lower Salmon Plant of the Great Shoshone and Twin Falls Water Power Company - ca. 1914 (Box 53)
      - 127 - Ames, Colorado - drawing of Ames Power Station - 1890 (Box 40)
      - 128 - Beaver River - mounted photos of cottage and station - n.d. (Box 57)
      - 129 - Camp Bird Divide - "Special Bent in Winter" - n.d. (Box 57)
      - 130 - Ophir Pass - view from the southwest - n.d. (Box 57)
      - 131- Beaver - 50th Anniversary of Telluride Power Company - photocopies - n.d. (Box 57)
      - 132 - Olmsted - views facing north - 1909 (Box 57)
      - 133 - Olmsted - Sunset Mountain - n.d. (Box 57)
      - 134 - Telluride - postcard - n.d. (Box 53)
      - 135 - unidentified location - construction at an unidentified site - from L.L. Nunn's desk - group and area photos - n.d (Box 53)
      - 136 - unidentified location - dam at unidentified site - 1908 (Box 53)
      - 137 - Ilium and Ames - captioned photos annotated and commented on by H.R. Lamb - 1910-1911, 4 envelopes (Box 58)
      - 138 - Ames - early construction - 1906, 4 envelopes (Box 58)
      - 139 - various locations - photo enlargements of early power installations, environs, etc. - n.d., 8 envelopes (Box 59)
      - 140 - Ames - high trestle above Ames - n.d. (Box 59)
      - 141 - Ophir - unidentified people at Ophir Pass - n.d. (Box 59)
      - 142 - Ames - original Ames plant - printed photo - n.d. (Box 62)
      - 143 - Jordan Narrows? - negative from Ted Munroe - annotated - n.d. (Box 62)
      - 144 - Olmsted - sites, structures, groups - negatives from Ted Munroe - n.d., 16 envelopes (Box 62)
    - B. Deep Springs
      - 1 - Deep Springs - photographs of Deep Springs album pages - ca. 1928, 15 envelopes (Box 33, 35)
      - 2 - Deep Springs and other US sites - photographs from W. Balderston's photo album - 1926-1934, 16 envelopes (Box 33, 34)
      - 3 - Deep Springs area and Yosemite - photographs from W. Balderston's photo album - 1932-33, 35 envelopes (Box 33, 34)
      - 4 - Deep Springs area and Death Valley - photographs W. Balderston's photo album - 1930-1932, 79 envelopes (Box 33, 34)
      - 5 - Deep Springs area - area landscapes, group photographs, ranch buildings - n.d., 71 envelopes (Box 52)
      - 6 - Deep Springs - early Deep Springs photos - ca. 1918, 4 envelopes (Box 38)
      - 7 - Deep Springs - informal individual and group photographs, grounds and structures - ca. 197-1947, 5 envelopes (Box 38)
      - 8 - Deep Springs area - Upper Ranch and surroundings - n.d., 5 envelopes (Box 38)
      - 9 - Deep Springs - Deep Springs Convention - 1968, 6 envelopes (Box 48)
      - 10 - Deep Springs - student body and area photos - ca. 1940, 5 envelopes (Box 47)
      - 11 - Deep Springs - Christmas cards from the student body - n.d. (Box 57)
      - 12 - Deep Springs - structures and panoramas at Deep Springs - ca. 1938-1960, 4 envelopes (Box 57)
      - 13 - Deep Springs - sheets of photos (many identified) of student body members and buildings - 1931-1944, 3 envelopes (Box 57)
      - 14 - Deep Springs - sheets of photos of Deep Springs under construction and student body members - annotated - ca. 1908, 1918-1927, 1931-1939, 2 envelopes (Box 57)
      - 15 - Deep Springs - Deep Springs Valley from Gilbert Pass - 1933 (Box 57)
      - 16 - Deep Springs - panorama- donated by A.A. Ross - 1918 (Box 40)
    - C. Telluride Association/House
      - 1 - Telluride House, Cornell, and Ithaca area - Telluride house interiors and exteriors, group photographs - 1910-1956, 66 envelopes (Box 50)
      - 2 - Boise, Idaho - Boise Branch Telluride Association - n.d., 2 envelopes (Box 36)
      - 3 - Telluride House, Deep Springs, and Electrical Mine and Mill Sites - negatives and portraits probably taken by Orville Sweeting - 1961-1968, 51 envelopes (Box 47)
      - 4 - Olmsted, Ithaca/Cornell, Grace, Boise, etc. - Paul P. Ashworth's photo album - ca. 1911-1916, 1937, 1954 (Box 52)
      - 5 - Deep Springs, Ocean City, various locations - photo album probably owned by Orville Sweeting - ca. 1940-1945 (Box 54)
      - 6 - Cornell Campus, Algonquin Park, various locations - photo album probably owned by Orville Sweeting - ca. 1940-1945 (Box 54)
      - 7 - Bliss, Beaver Canyon, Claremont - annotated notebook of negatives received from Paul Jones - 1913, 1914-1916 (Box 58)
      - 8 - various locations - extra copies of photos taken by Orville Sweeting for Telluride Association History Project - ca. 1963-1968, 4 envelopes (Box 57)
    - D. Miscellaneous and Unidentified
      - Miscellaneous photos (Box 26)
      - Miscellaneous photos (Box 27)
        Includes copy of the Telluride Journal for December 30, 1899.
      - Miscellaneous items (Box 28)
      - 1 - unidentified scenic enlargements - ca. 1920's, 11 envelopes (Box 36)
      - Photographs, Sweeting, Telluride, Omsted (Box 43)
      - 2 - unidentified photographs of photographs - mostly scenic, mills, etc. - n.d., 44 envelopes (Box 48)
      - 3 - Routt County, Unita, Duchesne Valley, etc. - pack trains, area photography, group photos - 1906-1907, 9 envelopes (Box 48)
      - 4 - unidentified site - n.d., 6 envelopes (Box 44)
      - 5 - California - unidentified photos of California from AM Wrench papers, 2 envelopes (Box 44)
      - 6 - Bald Rock Canyon, Feather River, etc. - n.d. (Box 44)
      - 7 - Yellowstone - junction of Firehole and Gibbon rivers - n.d. (Box 44)
      - 8 - Various locations world wide - unidentified negatives of various vacation photos in the US and Europe - ca. 1910's, 108 envelopes (Box 37)
      - 9 - unlabeled color photo - possibly Deep Springs - n.d. (Box 37)
      - 10 - unidentified mountain terrain photos - n.d., 3 envelopes (Box 48)
      - 11 - extra prints from Mrs. Helen Heckman - n.d., 22 envelopes (Box 53)
      - 12 - negatives from Ms. Helen C. Atwater - n.d., ca. 1900s-1910s, 43 envelopes (Box 47)
      - 13 - unidentified negatives - one portrait, one street scene - n.d. (Box 47)
      - 14 - Rockford, Illinois - postcard of Dr. Broughton's Sanitarium - n.d. (Box 48)
      - 15 - photographs from Ms. Helen C. Atwater - n.d. (Box 57)
      - 16 - Salt Lake City - photo of "Royal Kerman Shah Rug" - n.d. (Box 40)
      - 17 - unidentified location - waterfall - n.d. (Box 40)
      - 18 - mounted photo of unidentified wagon - "Mr. Buck" - n.d. (Box 40)
      - Telluride Photographs 1 (Box 2)
        Mounted landscape photos of Telluride, Colorado, and of Upper Lake West
      - Telluride Photographs 2 (Box 2)
        Mounted photos of houses, landscapes, and unnamed individuals from the Telluride area
      - Telluride Photographs 3 (Box 2)
        Mounted portrait photos of two unnamed individuals and one landscape entitled "Grandeur" from top of Mt. Wilson
      - Photograph negative cans (Box 71)
        10 film cannisters, 2 unlabeled, others seem to be Deep Springs related, JE68DSVLYDYR, JE68TACONVDS, Rabbi Tears, 68 DS 50th Reunion Roberts Ranch, Bristlcone PNES, Sierra Whtnyprtl
  - Photo Negatives
    - Bear Creek Area 1 (Box 53)
      4 unlabeled negatives
    - Bear Creek Area 2 (Box 53)
      17 labeled negatives
    - Bear Creek Area 3 (Box 53)
      12 labeled negatives
    - Bear Creek Area 4 (Box 53)
      9 unlabeled negatives
    - Bear Creek Area 5 (Box 53)
      2 labeled negatives
    - Bear Creek Photo Negatives 1 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Bear Creek Photo Negatives 2 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Bear Creek Photo Negatives 3 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - People: Portraiture, Individual, and Group Photographs
    - A. Electrical, Mining, and Mill Interests
      - 1 - Casper - group photos - 1916, 2 envelopes
      - 2 - Provo - unidentified - probably pinheads - ca. 1910's (Box 35)
      - 3 - Olmsted - individual and group photographs - 1907-1910, 10 envelopes (Box 42)
      - 4 - Provo - Pinheads at flume - 1907 -1908 (Box 44)
      - 5 - Font du Lac - Virginia Thornhill and lambs at Font du Lac - 1905 (Box 44)
      - 6 - Glenwood Springs - Max Rafferty (Box 44)
      - 7 - Olmsted - individual and group photographs - 1906-1909, 3 envelopes (Box 44)
      - 8 - Olmsted - Robert Hamilton - 1912 (Box 44)
      - 9 - Olmsted - individual and group photographs - 1906, 1909, 4 envelopes (Box 44)
      - 10 - Olmsted - pinheads at Olmsted - n.d., 3 envelopes (Box 44)
      - 11 - Olmsted - JC Miller and family - 1912 (Box 44)
      - 12 - Telluride area - group photographs, mostly from Edward Hoffer - ca. 1909-1911, 7 envelopes (Box 46)
      - 13 - Grace - Mrs. Fred M. Biersach - 1910 (Box 42)
      - 14 - Salt Lake area - Bert Woodhouse with wheel, group picture - ca. 1910, 2 envelopes (Box 41)
      - 15 - Telluride Colo. - Telluride Institute baseball game - ca. 1910-1911, 2 envelopes (Box 41)
      - 16 - Ilium, Colo. - group photographs, Clayton Grandy, Eddie Walters, 9 envelopes (Box 41)
      - 17 - Beaver, Colo. - Pinheads at Beaver - 1915-1916, 3 envelopes (Box 37)
      - 18 - Olmsted, etc. - individuals and groups, probably from Ted Munroe negatives - ca. 1900-1910, 13 envelopes (Box 41)
      - 19 - Olmsted - South Fork, group camping at Ed (Meehan)'s cabin - 1908-1909, 3 envelopes (Box 41)
      - 20 - Olmsted - David Wegg - 1910, 2 envelopes (Box 41)
      - 21 - Olmsted - unidentified group, area photographs - n.d., 2 envelopes (Box 41)
      - 22 - Olmsted - group photographs of pinheads, "Nightshirt Parade" - 1905-1908, 3 envelopes (Box 41)
      - 23 - Battle Creek - David Wegg and surveying gang - 1905, 2 envelopes (Box 41)
      - 24 - Olmsted - CN Whitman - n.d. (Box 47)
      - 25 - Olmsted - snow slide at Bridal Veil, break in flume, clearing crews - 1909, 12 envelopes (Box 44)
      - 26 - Olmsted - buildings, grounds, individual and group photographs - ca. 1908, 1909, 1910, 1937, 8 envelopes (Box 37)
      - 27 - Idaho - Pocatello Power Plant, and Bliss - n.d., 1913, 1914, 7 envelopes (Box 37)
      - 28 - Idaho - Grace and Malad River - landscapes and informal photos - 1912, ca. 1910, 3 envelopes (Box 45)
      - 29 - Ontario - Niagara - ice jam, plant construction, informal photographs - 1906-1914, 12 envelopes (Box 45)
      - 30 - Olmsted - pinheads at Olmsted - ca. 1908 (Box 45)
      - 31 - Olmsted - pinheads, staff, and structures at Olmsted - 1904-1905, 5 envelopes (Box 53)
      - 32 - Provo - mounted portrait of F.M. Blackburn, bookkeeper - n.d. (Box 53)
      - 33 - Olmsted, Ithaca/Cornell, Grace, Boise, etc. - Paul P. Ashworth's photo album - ca. 1911-1916, 1937, 1954 (Box 52)
      - 34 - Nunn's Station - group and individual photos - n.d. (Box 53)
      - 35 - Nunn's Station - man with equipment - n.d. (Box 53)
      - 36 - various locations - informal photos of David Wegg and friends - ca. 1910, 6 envelopes (Box 47, 58)
      - 36 - various locations - informal photos of David Wegg and friends - ca. 191037 - Olmsted - Telluride Associates - annotations enclosed - 1911-1914, 2 envelopes (Box 57)
      - 38 - Beaver, Colorado - Chet Dunn at Beaver - 1915, 1916 (Box 47)
      - 39 - various locations - photos of Pinheads, Associates, etc. - ca. 1911-1961, 18 envelopes (Box 47, 58)
      - 40 - Olmsted - group photos, baseball game, Christmas, etc. - 1908-1910, 12 envelopes (Box 47, 58)
      - 41 - unidentified location - man at switchboard, probably P.P. Ashworth - n.d. (Box 47)
      - 42 - Olmsted - Olmsted 50th Anniversary Celebration - 1961 (Box 57)
      - 43 - Telluride - line construction - n.d. (Box 57)
      - 44 - unidentified location - Charles Walcott, Dave and Jack Bonnett with bear - 1908 (Box 57)
      - 45 - Governor/Nunn's Station - Eugene Smith - 1902 (Box 57)
      - 46 - Bridal Veil pump station - pinheads - 1908 (Box 57)
      - 47 - unidentified location - unidentified group at electrical site - n.d. (Box 57)
      - 48 - Nunn's Station - group photo and Bristoe (Frank C. Noon's brother-in-law) - 1901, ca. 1901-1902, 2 envelopes (Box 57)
      - 49 - Olmsted - annotated photo of "The Bunch" at Olmsted - n.d. (Box 57)
      - 50 - Beaver - 50th Anniversary of Telluride Power Company - photocopies - n.d. (Box 57)
      - 51 - Olmsted - David S. Wegg Jr. - 1910 (Box 57)
      - 52 - Olmsted - Ed P. Woodhouse - 1910 (Box 57)
      - 53 - Olmsted - Paul O. Reyneau - 1910 (Box 57)
      - 54 - Olmsted - John Olmsted on the stoop of quarters - 1909 (Box 57)
      - 55 - unidentified location - construction at an unidentified site - from L.L. Nunn's desk - group and area photos - n.d. (Box 53)
      - 56 - Ilium and Ames - captioned photos annotated and commented on by H.R. Lamb - 1910-1911, 4 envelopes (Box 58)
      - 57 - Olmsted - enlargements of group photo - n.d. (Box 59)
      - 58 - Ophir - unidentified people at Ophir Pass - n.d. (Box 59)
      - 59 - Provo area? - Ted Munroe and Zella Farrer - negative from Ted Munroe- annotated in 1961 - n.d. (Box 62)
      - 60 - Olmsted - sites, structures, groups - negatives from Ted Munroe - n.d., 16 envelopes (Box 62)
    - B. Deep Springs
      - 1 - Deep Springs - photographs of Deep Springs album pages, 15 envelopes (Box 35)
      - 2 - Deep Springs and other US sites - photographs from W. Balderston's photo album - 1926-1934, 34 envelopes (Box 33)
      - 3 - Deep Springs area and Yosemite - photographs from W. Balderston's photo album - 1932-1933, 32 envelopes (Box 33)
      - 4 - Deep Springs area and Death Valley - photographs W. Balderston's photo album - 1930-1932, 72 envelopes (Box 33)
      - 5 - Deep Springs area - area landscapes, group photographs, ranch buildings - n.d., 71 envelopes (Box 48)
      - 6 - Deep Springs - early pictures, group pictures, etc. - 1919-1927 (Box 38)
      - 7 - Deep Springs - annual Student Body photos - 1918-1961, 37 envelopes (Box 38)
      - 8 - Deep Springs - informal individual and group photographs, grounds and structures - ca. 197-1947, 5 envelopes (Box 38)
      - 9 - Deep Springs - negatives of campus and surrounding areas - ca. 1968 - 29 envelopes - Box 56, 29 envelopes (Box 37)
      - 10 - Deep Springs - action shots of student labor taken for brochure - one photo annotated - ca. 1930s, 5 envelopes (Box 57)
      - 11 - Deep Springs - student body and area photos - ca. 1940, 5 envelopes (Box 47)
      - 12 - Deep Springs - student body and staff - 1916-1917, 2 envelopes (Box 47)
      - 13 - Deep Springs - round up and branding - 1917-1918 (Box 47)
      - 14 - Deep Springs - Ed Woodhouse - 1919 (Box 47)
      - 15 - Deep Springs - Henderson, Johnson - 1947 (Box 47)
      - 16 - Deep Springs - E.M. Johnson - 1940, 1943-1944 (Box 47)
      - 17 - Deep Springs - Robley Williams, W.B. Biersach Sr., Lewis Lawrence, Prof. Nevil Sedgwick, Howard Turner - 1938-1939 (Box 47)
      - 18 - Deep Springs - Chester "Chet" Dunn - 1968 (Box 57)
      - 19 - Deep Springs - student body members - ca. 1940, 4 envelopes (Box 57)
      - 20 - Deep Springs - sheets of photos (many identified) of student body members and buildings - 1931-1944, 3 envelopes (Box 57)
      - 21 - Deep Springs - sheets of photos of Deep Springs under construction and student body members - annotated - ca. 1908, 1918-1927, 1931-1939, 2 envelopes (Box 57)
      - 22 - Deep Springs - unidentified group photo - "Grads"? - 1934 (Box 40)
      - 23 - Deep Springs - Telluride and Deep Springs Reunion - 1968, 3 envelopes (Box 57)
      - Harvey C. Mansfield photonegative album, April 1-10, 1924; CD-2221 (Box 57)
        Shows people and activities at Deep Springs. An index to the negatives is in the back of the book and includes names of those pictured, Including P.N. Nunn, Willsie Martin, Carl S. Patton, Frayne S. Williams, R. G. Baumgardt, Livingston Porter, Carl S. Patton, Anthony F. Blanks, Edna Brush Perkins, Pat Hughes and others. This album has been digitized on CD-2221.
      - Two Deep Springs images., 1948, undated (Box 57)
        Joe Kershaw, Mary Anne and their son, Harvey and Grace at mine tunnel in Gilbert Pass. Also Clarence Yarrow and Bob Cavenaugh.
    - C. Telluride Association/House
      - Group photographs, 1910-1961 (Box 69)
        CD-1839 with ID's, in accession folder
      - 1 - portraits of Telluride Association members - ca. 1910's, 8 envelopes (Box 46)
      - 2 - Telluride House, Cornell, and Ithaca area - Telluride house interiors and exteriors, group photographs - 1910-1956, 36, 48 envelopes
      - 3 - Olmsted - Telluride Association Constitutional Convention, annotated photograph - 1911, 3 envelopes
      - 4 - Boise, Idaho - Telluride Association Boise Branch - 1913 (Box 36)
      - 5 - Ithaca area - Telluride Association Summer Programs (TASP) - 1954-1956, 4 envelopes (Box 36, 47)
      - 6- Ithaca area - Olin and Gatje at 1953 convention, Roodhouse portrait - 1953 (Box 48)
      - 7 - Charles D. Walcott, secretary of Smithsonian - n.d. (Box 48)
      - 8 - unidentified numbered photographs - 1911 (Box 48)
      - 9 - Bliss, Idaho, Malad River, Cornell - negatives from Dan Lindsay - n.d., 2 envelopes (Box 48)
      - 10 - Olmsted, Ithaca/Cornell, Grace, Boise, etc. - Paul P. Ashworth's photo album - ca. 1911-1916, 1937, 1954 (Box 52)
      - 11 - Deep Springs, Ocean City, various locations - photo album probably owned by Orville Sweeting - ca. 1940-1945 (Box 54)
      - 12 - Cornell Campus, Algonquin Park, various locations - photo album probably owned by Orville Sweeting - ca. 1940-1945 (Box 54)
      - 13 - Cornell University - portrait of George Lincoln Burr - 1922, after 1922, 2 envelopes (Box 57)
      - 14 - Cornell University - A.D. White, William Howard Taft, and Jacob Gould Schurman - n.d. (Box 57)
      - 15 - Cornell and Ithaca - area photos donated by W.D. Johnston - 1913-1916, 9 envelopes (Box 40, 57)
      - 16 - Cornell University - annotated crew team photo and certificates to P.P. Ashworth - 1913-1914 (Box 40)
      - 17 - mounted portrait of E.D. Fournier inscribed to Telluride Association - 1913 (Box 40)
      - 18 - Deep Springs - Telluride and Deep Springs Reunion - 1968 (Box 57)
      - 19 - Cornell University - Telluride House group photo - ca. 1950s? (Box 47)
      - Scrapbook, War portraits, aerial campus view (Box 66)
      - Convention Photographs 1911-1960 (Box 67)
    - D. Miscellaneous and Unidentified
      - 1 - A.A. Ross and family - 1958, 5 envelopes (Box 37)
      - 2 - Routt County, Unita, Duchesne Valley, etc. - pack trains, area photography, group photos - 1906-1907, 9 envelopes (Box 48)
      - 3 - California - unidentified photos of California from A.M. Wrench papers, 2 envelopes (Box 44)
      - 4 - annotated photographs, possibly former Pinheads - 1929, 3 envelopes (Box 47)
      - 5 - David MacRitchie - n.d. (Box 44)
      - 6 - unidentified men at rail site
      - 7 - unidentified man - n.d. (Box 47)
      - 8 - Various locations world wide - unidentified negatives of various vacation photos in the US and Europe - ca. 1910's, 108 envelopes (Box 37)
      - 9 - extra prints from Mrs. Helen Heckman - n.d., 27 envelopes (Box 53)
      - 10 - negatives from Ms. Helen C. Atwater - n.d., ca. 1900s-1910s, 43 envelopes (Box 47)
      - 11 - Telluride House, Deep Springs, and Electrical Mine and Mill Sites - negatives and portraits probably taken by Orville Sweeting - 1961-1968, 51 envelopes (Box 47)
      - 12-Deep Springs - Deep Springs Convention - 1968, 6 envelopes (Box 48)
      - 13 - portrait of Fredric L. Barbours - ca. 1916 - autograph enclosed (Box 49)
      - 14 - Cornell - unidentified young men - ca. 1915 (Box 49)
      - 15 - unidentified informal portrait - n.d. (Box 47)
      - 16 - 2 postcard portraits, one from F.J. Loscy - n.d. (Box 48)
      - 17 - miscellaneous identified photographs - various dates, 3 envelopes (Box 47, 58)
      - 18 - miscellaneous unidentified photographs - various dates, 8 envelopes (Box 40, 47, 49, 53)
      - 19 - Niagara - J.R. Bronystone? - ca. 1915 (Box 49)
      - 20 - photos of unidentified children - probably Sweeting children - n.d., 3 envelopes (Box 58)
  - Technical Photographs
    - 1 - Casper - technical equipment at plant - 1916 (Box 42)
    - 2 - Olmsted - reinstallation - 1908 (Box 42)
    - 3 - Olmsted - second mudslide, excavation, flume construction - 1909 (Box 42)
    - 4 - Olmsted - runner east turbine - 1906 (Box 42)
    - 5 - Olmsted - roller on road - 1910 (Box 42)
    - 6 - Olmsted - preparation and turbine installation - 1908-1909 (Box 44)
    - 7 - unidentified equipment, damaged - n.d. (Box 42)
    - 8 - Olmsted - unidentified equipment - n. d. (Box 44)
    - 9 - Olmsted - insulator testing - 1909 (Box 44)
    - 10 - Olmsted - new standard construction, centerline - 1908 (Box 44)
    - 11 - Logan - landscapes, units, generator, etc. at Logan station - n.d., 7 envelopes (Box 35)
    - 12 - Grace - equipment at Grace station - 1907-1910, 14 envelopes (Box 42)
    - 13 - Salt Lake area - Salt Lake to Ogden line, construction, etc. - ca. 1910, 4 envelopes (Box 41)
    - 14 - Ames/Ophir - area photographs and technical equipment - ca. 1900's, 114 envelopes (Box 33, 34)
    - 15 - Telluride area - photographs of Ames/Ophir/Trout Lake area - ca. 1909-1910, 21 envelopes (Box 33, 34)
    - 16 - Trout Lake - construction at Trout Lake reservoir - ca. 1910-1911 (Box 41)
    - 17 - Nunn's Station - station interior, unit under construction, etc. - 1901-1902, 3 envelopes (Box 41)
    - 18 - Olmsted - generators, turbine, pressure box, etc. - n.d., 5 envelopes (Box 37)
    - 19 - Olmsted, etc. - prints from Ted Munroe negatives, installations, etc. - ca. 1900-1910, 18 envelopes (Box 41)
    - 20 - Olmsted - blueprints of area photos and designs - n.d., 6 envelopes (Box 41)
    - 21 - Olmsted - 5000 volt line - 1907 (Box 41)
    - 22 - Olmsted - erosion of flume lining - 1909 (Box 41)
    - 23 - Olmsted - hydraulic filling and penstocks - 1909 (Box 41)
    - 24 - Battle Creek - high tension room, generator, Pelton wheel, etc. - ca. 1909, 3 envelopes (Box 41, 42)
    - 25 - Boise, Idaho - "After the Night Before" - n.d. (Box 47)
    - 26 - Creeping Grip tractor - n.d. (Box 44)
    - 27 - Ontario Power Plant - detailed floor plans and technical drawings - n.d., 40 envelopes (Box 39, 45)
    - 28 - Mexico - LLuvia de Oro, Chorro, etc., construction, buildings, etc. - ca. 1907, 17 envelopes (Box 45)
    - 29 - Olmsted - grounding device at Olmsted - 1909 (Box 45)
    - 30 - Grace, Idaho - equipment at Grace - 1910 (Box 45)
    - 31 - Logan Canyon, Utah - Logan Station, equipment and building interiors - ca. 1910, 2 envelopes (Box 45)
    - 32 - Front Lake, Ophir Pass - Ophir Pass and pipe at Front Lake - n.d. (Box 45)
    - 33 - Utah - transmission lines near Narrows Station - 1908-1909 (Box 45)
    - 34 - Olmsted - penstocks under construction -n.d. (Box 45)
    - 35 - Grace, Idaho - station interior, powerhouse, etc. - ca. 1907, 1910, 12 envelopes (Box 45)